So cute.
かわいいな
Why?
なぜなの?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してますね
Are you with your boyfriend?
彼氏と一緒にしてる?
it is?
それは?
I just had a nosebleed.
さっき鼻血出ちゃったよ
You saw it, right?
見たよね?
Are you going to give your boyfriend a nosebleed already?
彼氏にもう鼻血出させるの?
Your skin is so beautiful.
すっごい肌きれいだね
You're pushing your feet.
足押ししてるね
So beautiful
めっちゃ綺麗
That's right.
だ ね
It's really beautiful.
め っちゃ綺麗だね
Oh, that's amazing.
あ、すごいね
A lot came out.
い っぱい出てきたよ
Why this?
なんでこれ?
Did you cry?
涙しちゃったの?
Awesome.
すっごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It was amazing.
すごいなって
Awesome.
すんごい
or
や
times.
ばい
That's amazing.
す んごいね
Are you full?
お腹いっぱい?
It seems possible.
できそう
Wait a minute, I'm here.
ちょっともうさ、ここに来たわ
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
copper?
どう?
terrible.
やばい
It feels really good though.
めちゃめちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
terrible.
やばい
I can't move.
動けない
What should I do?
どうしよう
It feels really good though.
めちゃめちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
terrible.
やばい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
terrible.
やばい
It feels really good.
め ちゃ めちゃ気持ちいい
terrible.
やばい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Let's bring it out again.
また出そう
It flew great.
すんごい飛んだ
Something's wrong with me today.
なんかもう今日おかしいわ
I fired two shots.
2発も出しちゃった
Strangely enough, I fired two shots.
変に2発も出しちゃった
I wanted to serve it even if it tasted bad.
味かかっても出したくなった
amazing.
すごい
I put it out in a strange way.
変な出し方しちゃった
how was it?
どうだった?
It happened three times.
3回も出ちゃったよ
It appeared three times and ended up in a strange position.
3回も出て変な 変 な位置になっちゃった
Was it okay?
大丈夫だったかな?
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね